In this tutorial video, we use the 11th version of DOS Marvelous Designer.
If you need to learn the 10th version of Marvelous Designer, please watch the previous video.
In order to make it easier to learn, DOS is used in this tutorial.
Under the file option of the main menu, we can see the various file types supported by Marvelous Designer.
You can import or export any file type supported by Marvelous Designer.
Let's try to import a file first.
Click on the file option in the main menu to choose whether to import or import.
Click on the appropriate file type and select the file to be imported.
After selecting, a pop-up window will pop up.
Select the appropriate option according to your needs.
After clicking OK, the object will appear in the window.
Importing files is also a similar method.
Click on the file option in the main menu to find the export option and select the appropriate file type.
Select the path to export, set the name, select the appropriate option in the pop-up window,
click on OK to complete the export.
You can store your files in two formats, project files or costume files.
If you store the file as a project file, the entire project, including virtual model information, animation files and costume files, etc. will be stored.
If you choose to store it as a costume file, the file will only store costume and other related information, and there will be no other content.